var questions = [{

    "question": "What is the rarest card in the whole Pokemon card game?",
    "option1": "Mewtwo",
    "option2": "Magikarp",
    "option3": "Charizard",
    "option4": "Pikachua",
    "answer": "3"

}, {

    "question": "How many trainer item cards can you play per turn?",
    "option1": "one",
    "option2": "unlimited",
    "option3": "three",
    "option4": "two",
    "answer": "2"  
}, {
    
    "question": "How many supporter cards can you play per turn?",
    "option1": "three",
    "option2": "two",
    "option3": "unlimited",
    "option4": "one",
    "answer": "4"   
}, {

    "question": "How many card do you start out with in your hand?",
    "option1": "five",
    "option2": "seven",
    "option3": "three",
    "option4": "As many as your opponent chooses",
    "answer": "2"   


}, {

    "question": "What the pokemon attack that you can only do once per game?",
    "option1": "GX Attack",
    "option2": "EX Attack",
    "option3": "PX Attack",
    "option4": "Super Awesome Attack",
    "answer": "1"   


}, {

    "question": "What special Enegries can apply for multiple pokemon types?",
    "option1": "Prism",
    "option2": "Rainbow",
    "option3": "Blend",
    "option4": "All of the above",
    "answer": "4"   
}, {

    "question": "When are you allow to attack on your turn?",
    "option1": "Beginning of turn",
    "option2": "Middle of turn",
    "option3": "End of turn",
    "option4": "Doesnt Matter",
    "answer": "3"

},{

    "question": "How many pokemon can you have on your bench?",
    "option1": "3",
    "option2": "none",
    "option3": "6",
    "option4": "5",
    "answer": "4"

}, {

    "question": "How many card can you have in your deck with the same name?",
    "option1": "3",
    "option2": "4",
    "option3": "5",
    "option4": "unlimited",
    "answer": "2"
}, {

    "question": "How many cards are you allowed to have in your deck?",
    "option1": "40",
    "option2": "50",
    "option3": "60",
    "option4": "100",
    "answer": "3"

}]